<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on 姜跃锋</title>
    <link>https://jyfnote.netlify.app/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on 姜跃锋</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 21:13:14 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jyfnote.netlify.app/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>https://jyfnote.netlify.app/2014/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jyfnote.netlify.app/2014/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title>
      <link>https://jyfnote.netlify.app/2014/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jyfnote.netlify.app/2014/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>https://jyfnote.netlify.app/2020/2020-12-01-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jyfnote.netlify.app/2020/2020-12-01-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R MarkdownThis is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars)## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>https://jyfnote.netlify.app/2014/goisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jyfnote.netlify.app/2014/goisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent Go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in Go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using Go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://jyfnote.netlify.app/2014/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jyfnote.netlify.app/2014/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Go to Hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your OS and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at Install Hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
Clone the Hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313 Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction aux modèles (Hu)go</title>
      <link>https://jyfnote.netlify.app/2014/goisforlovers.fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jyfnote.netlify.app/2014/goisforlovers.fr/</guid>
      <description>Hugo utilise l&amp;rsquo;excellente librairie go html/template pour son moteur de modèles. c&amp;rsquo;est un moteur extrêmement léger qui offre un très petit nombre de fonctions logiques. À notre expérience, c&amp;rsquo;est juste ce qu&amp;rsquo;il faut pour créer un bon site web statique. Si vous avez déjà utilisé d&amp;rsquo;autre moteurs de modèles pour différents langages ou frameworks, vous allez retrouver beaucoup de similitudes avec les modèles go.
Ce document est une introduction sur l&amp;rsquo;utilisation de Go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://jyfnote.netlify.app/1/%E5%9F%8E%E5%B8%82%E5%BB%BA%E6%88%90%E5%8C%BA%E6%97%B6%E7%A9%BA%E6%BC%94%E5%8F%98%E5%8F%8A%E9%A9%B1%E5%8A%A8%E5%9B%A0%E7%B4%A0%E5%88%86%E6%9E%90%E4%B8%AD%E5%9B%BD%E5%8C%97%E6%96%B9%E5%92%8C%E5%8D%97%E6%96%B9%E5%85%B8%E5%9E%8B%E5%9F%8E%E5%B8%82%E7%9A%84%E6%AF%94%E8%BE%83/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jyfnote.netlify.app/1/%E5%9F%8E%E5%B8%82%E5%BB%BA%E6%88%90%E5%8C%BA%E6%97%B6%E7%A9%BA%E6%BC%94%E5%8F%98%E5%8F%8A%E9%A9%B1%E5%8A%A8%E5%9B%A0%E7%B4%A0%E5%88%86%E6%9E%90%E4%B8%AD%E5%9B%BD%E5%8C%97%E6%96%B9%E5%92%8C%E5%8D%97%E6%96%B9%E5%85%B8%E5%9E%8B%E5%9F%8E%E5%B8%82%E7%9A%84%E6%AF%94%E8%BE%83/</guid>
      <description>城市建成区时空演变及驱动因素分析——中国北方和南方典型城市的比较 摘要 城市扩张是城市化的重要表现。基于不透水表面聚集密度（ISAD）方法，本研究提取了1995年至2015年中国北方和南方12个主要城市的城市建成区（UBA）范围。综合运用城市重心、分形维数、紧凑度、城市空间形态扩展模式、城市扩展速度等指标，探索城市扩展的时空演化特征。使用统计方法Geodector（GD）分析经济、交通、自然环境和社会因素对城市扩张的影响。结果表明，12个城市具有不同的扩张特征和时空演化特征。大多数北方城市有单核心扩张，而大多数南方城市有多核心扩张。城市的空间形态大多趋于离散化，南方城市的扩张过程明显快于北方城市。测地仪显示，北部和南部的城市扩张主要与人口和经济有关。社会因素解释了南部城市的扩张，虽然强度比北部城市强，但自然因素相反，交通因素没有显著差异。这一分析证实了中国北方和南方经济发展的差异，为制定全国范围的城市发展政策提供了科学参考。在全球城市化的背景下，本研究的结果将为了解城市扩张的时空特征提供一个中国样本，对世界其他国家和地区，尤其是发展中国家的城市化研究具有很好的参考价值。</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
